Curriculum Vitae

Personal Particulars

Name: Tsang Chi Tat / Arthur

Email: chitattsang@gmail.com

Phone: 5282 1440

Website: https://chitattsang.github.io/



Summary

I worked as an IT Technician in a school for three months. In the course of my work, I was not competitive enough, so I resigned from my job and completed the course of Certificate in Creative Digital Media Design and Production Assistant Training and Certificate in Web Development Training. As a short-term goal, I would like to deepen my technical skills through my work. As a long-term goal, I am willing to become a developer. I hope you can provide me with another opportunity to practice what I've learned.

Technical Skills

- Understand and can use 3D and 2D software, like Blender.
- Proficiency in open source software, such as LibreOffice, Inkscape, Kurta, GIMP, OpenShot, etc.
- Knowledge in React JS, JavaScript, HTML and CSS programming language.
- Frequent user of Microsoft Office programs.

Technical Project

Front End Developer Trainee, training course organized by Christian Action and Xccelerate

Period : From 24 Oct 2023 to 17 Feb 2024 Intern : From 29 Jan 2024 to 17 Feb 2024

Remark : My capstone project is to support client's (Space is Limited) content pages setup in Content Management System optimization work. Our team's optimized website link is https://exp.is/exploration

Creative Digital Media Design and Production Assistant Training Trainee, training course organized by Scope, City University of Hong Kong and Krystal Technology Limited

Period : From 31 Oct 2023 to 21 Dec 2023

Remark : My final project is to create a new snack, which is made from Korean honey cheese fried chicken and Japanese cherry blossom matcha. You can see the final product of our group on my website.

Working Experience

IT Technician, HK & KLN Chiu Chow Public Assn Secondary School

Period: From 07 July 2023 to 30 September 2023

Duties: Provides high-quality remote assistance and onsite support for the hardware of the CCPASS. Responsible for developing manuals and training materials to help teachers learn how to use various applications, software and hardware. Experience in FUJI XEROX DocuCentre-VII C5573, RICOH MP C2004, CANON iR-ADV C5550/5560 III Printer Setup and Configuration.

IT Technician, World Wide P.C.B. Equipments Company Limited

Period: From 20 February 2023 to 19 June 2023

Duties: Provides high-quality remote assistance and onsite support for the hardware of the World Wide Group. Experience in PC/Printer Setup and Configuration, Desktop/Laptop Support, Hardware Support, Documentation, Inventory Management, End-user Support.

IT Engineer, Primetech Technology Limited

Period: From 26 September 2022 to 14 January 2023

Duties: Provides high-quality remote assistance and onsite support for the hardware of the Jockey Club. Manage the inventory of hardware for E. C. Fix Technology Limited (like motherboard and power supply unit etc.). Vendor contracts concerning end-user equipment (like Dell, Lenovo and HPE etc.).

Service Engineer, IT-ec (HK) Limited

Period: From 27 June 2022 to 05 September 2022

Duties: Provides high-quality remote assistance and onsite support for the products of HP company.

Education Background

Higher Diploma Programme in Network and Mobile Computing, School of Continuing and Professional Studies (CUSCS), The Chinese University of Hong Kong Graduated in the academic year of 2013-2014.

Secondary Seven, Fanling Lutheran Secondary School (FLSS) Graduated in the academic year of 2009-2010.

Language

Cantonese, Mandarin and English

Availability

Immediate

Expected Salary

Negotiable